Guide to the Edward Luther Stevenson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1870-1941; Series III; 5; (12 boxes)
  - Notes, [ca. 1880s-1930s]
    - M.P.E. globes (Box 48, Folder 506)
    - Reformation (Box 48, Folder 507-508)
    - Renaissance (Box 48, Folder 509-510)
    - U.S. History (Box 48, Folder 511-515)
    - Vespucci, Juan; world map (Box 49, Folder 516)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 517-521)
  - Outlines, [ca.1880s-1930s]
    - American and European history (Box 49, Folder 522)
    - Beginning of civilization in Europe (Box 49, Folder 523)
    - Bibliographies
      - Astronomy books (Box 49, Folder 524)
      - Dante (Box 49, Folder 525)
      - Europe in Modern Times (Box 49, Folder 526)
      - History of Renaissance and Reformation (Box 50, Folder 527)
      - Maritime exploration and medieval maps (Box 50, Folder 528)
      - Middle Ages (Box 50, Folder 529)
      - Reformation (Box 50, Folder 530)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 531)
    - Development of Reformation (Box 50, Folder 532)
    - The Geography of the Middle Ages (Box 50, Folder 533)
    - History course (Box 50, Folder 534)
    - Luther (Box 50, Folder 535)
    - Maps of 15th and 16th centuries (Box 50, Folder 536)
    - Medieval history (Box 50, Folder 537)
    - Middle Ages (Box 50, Folder 538)
    - Physiography and archeology of the U.S. (Box 50, Folder 539)
    - Reformation (Box 50, Folder 540-541)
    - Reformation and Renaissance (Box 50, Folder 542)
    - Renaissance (Box 51, Folder 543-544)
    - Universal history (Box 51, Folder 545)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 546)
  - Student Papers
    - Heidelberg thesis
      - English version, 1890 (Box 51, Folder 547)
      - German version, 1888-1891 (Box 51, Folder 548-549)
    - German notebooks, 1888-1891 (Box 52, Folder 550-556)
    - German notebooks, 1888-1891 (Box 53, Folder 557-560)
  - Miscellanea
    - Astronomical photographs, [ca. 1921] (Box 53, Folder 561)
    - Comparative charts, undated (Box 53, Folder 562)
    - Exam questions, [ca. 1902-1909] (Box 53, Folder 563)
    - Gazeteer listings, undated (Box 54, Folder 564-565)
    - Hispanic Society of America, undated (Box 54, Folder 566)
    - Lists - miscellaneous, 1903-1934, undated (Box 54, Folder 567-568)
    - Notebooks of Stevenson's bibliography: typescripts of title pages, [ca. 1941] (Box 54, Folder 569-570)
    - Photostats of Stevenson's articles, 1904, 1907 (Box 54, Folder 571)
    - Real Academia Hispano America, 1922-1927 (Box 54, Folder 572)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 54, Folder 573)
    - Title pages, [ca. 1941] (Box 55, Folder 574)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 55, Folder 575-577)